psychz.net 2002-10-14

# Psychz: Customer Support - Privacy Policy

**Web Hosting Packages **

  * ** Ensim Control Panel**
  * 100 MB of space
  * 4 GB Monthly Bandwidth limit.
  * Unlimited POP3
  * Email Aliases
  * Unlimited Email responder
  * Unlimited auto responders
  * Unlimited sub domains
  * CGI usage
  * FTP access
  * Anonymous FTP  
  * Microsoft® FrontPage® Server Extension
  * MySql Database, PhpAdmin
  * Perl
  * Web Mail (Squirrel Mail)                       
  * Server Sides Include
  * support .php, .html, .shtml, and more
  * 99.99% uptime

_**MORE INFO**_   

| | 

_Privacy Policy of Psychz Web Solutions_

Psychz.net has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website:   
www.Psychz.net.

  * We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. 

  * Our site uses cookies to keep track of your shopping cart. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site.

  * This site contains links to other sites. Hosting-Network, Inc. is not responsible nor can it be held liable for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

  * We will not disclose or distribute your information to or with any third-parties, for whichever purpose it may be. Never will any third-party consciously gain access to your personal information.

  * Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect visitor's contact information (like their email address) and financial information (like their account or credit card numbers). Contact information from the order form is used to send orders and information about our company to our customers. The customer's contact information is also used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Financial information that is collected is used to check the users' qualifications and bill the user for products and services.   
**  
**  
**_Public Forums_**  
**  
** This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should   
exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. **  
  
**  
**_Security_** **  
**  
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. We have excellent anti-hacking software in place that was either purchased from third-parties and or programmed by our in-house developers. There is hardly any risk of information being compromised or accessed by any unauthorized parties. **  
  
**  
**_Choice/Opt-Out_** Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor. This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. You can send email to [ billing@Psychz.net](mailto:billing@Psychz.net)  

**_Correct/Update_**

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. Email: [ billing@Psychz.net](mailto:billing@Psychz.net)
